Yes everyone, so did you see the last video?
We are going to have a barbecue today at this beautiful place!
We did it! Last year we had some great quotes, the most delicious food, and a split...
I'm glad we can do it again this year!
And here we are! And here it is!
It's a gorgeous food! Thank you very much!
This time, the best!
The best!
We have prepared a lot of ingredients for the theme of "Let's have a barbecue"!
Thank you very much!
Let me introduce you.
Where would you like to start? When you think of barbecue, do you think of meat?
We really love beef tongue!
And by meat, I mean old kogi.
It's my first time.
I'm really looking forward to it!
And a very large chicken, please!
Thank you, meat!
And if you want to grill with the meat, here it is!
It's so heavy!
So heavy!
Vegetables
A lot of them!
Mushrooms nearby
Looks delicious!
Introducing
We have a lot of mushrooms!
Helpful, Helpful, Helpful, Elysian Sea. Icissar.
Mikuni Nori.
We have it again this year.
This year, too, it's in this table...
This is the size of Korean dried laver!
And cola!
We have them again this year!
We have about 30 bottles.
20 bottles each.
Oh, no, no, no.
We have 60 bottles.
You can drink 10 bottles each.
And here's a big one.
Yay!
You got more power.
I got more power, too.
I missed the macarons.
I'm telling the truth.
Macarons.
I'll tell you what I missed out on.
Chocolate and marshmallows
Because sweet things make me happy!
And... we're having a barbecue...
Yes, sir.
I'd like to get
I love it!
That's what I'm saying.
I've already got a request.
I've already had a request for a pattuemi, and I've already had a request for a pattuemi, and I'd like you all to join me for a meal and a barbecue.
Let's have fun barbecuing!
onions... you know... you have the image of an onion with a single whim.
It's not an onion.
The beach!
It reminds me of making curry in elementary school.
I remember making curry in elementary school.
I was going to buy some.
Taya, you know...
You put them in the other cart.
That's right.
Korean seaweed.
I was going to buy some this year.
It's called Quest, so I got the other one, the cart.
It's really interesting.
It was really funny.
I remembered it as I was cutting it up.
You remembered?
It was so embarrassing.
It was the funniest laugh of the day, and the most visible today.
She's so kind, with a nice voice and a friendly smile, like she'd do me in the sea.
Oh, my God!
me
4th не
Kira, power Less ring
Hit it!
It's great!
Mirei is the best as it is.
Is the beef tongue this big?
Yes, for sure.
Milby again.
Oh, my God, Kir?
It's Milby, Milay.
It's a good time.
It's not often you see such an upscale place.
I'm just starting to see it.
You're so good.
The manager's starting to take videos.
Here it is.
Oh, my God, he's getting better.
You're so good!
Maybe it's a little bit of a side skill.
A new one.
The three-step butchery?
Oh, yeah!
That's it!
That's amazing!
It takes skill to be able to insert the teeth vertically.
But it's definitely a good size, and it's a good size to eat.
Don't you think?
Thank you.
Great job, guys.
I'm gonna go for a run.
I'm good at it.
Triple-cut meat.
That's wonderful.
You know, I thought these onions wouldn't hurt at all.
What? It sure does.
That's amazing.
Or are my eyes just getting stronger?
Which is it?
Either the onions are very good.
And these mushrooms.
You should cut them up.
Do you think we can keep the shiitake mushrooms?
What do you think?
Cut them off!
Shall we cut them up?
Oh, maybe one more time.
Let's cut it here.
It's a good ride.
We're the oldest in Noemie.
We're the same age.
That's nice.
Barbecue.
Oh, my God! You're really good!
I'm so happy!
Three cuts!
That's so good!
That's great!
We did it!
We worked together!
We did a great job!
Doesn't it look great?
I'm going to bake it!
Go for it!
It's gonna burn!
Yes! It's gonna burn!
Yes!
Here you go!
Oh, my gosh!
Lamb roe.
Looks so good! All kinds of meat
They're sticking together! They're sticking together!
Our love of meat is showing, and there's no place to put the vegetables.
Oh, no!
I guess it's okay.
Wait, I think this is the meat.
I can't grab it.
Oh, my God.
You're good.
I knew I didn't get the part.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
You're good.
There's all kinds of pies.
Do you have any pies?
This looks so good.
It looks so good.
Thank you very much.
I don't like it.
So it's baked.
Yay!
Amazing, isn't it?
It's so gorgeous!
It's too gorgeous.
It's amazing! Shall we eat it right away?
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
Shall we toast?
This is the second barbecue of the same age group.
Let's have it together.
Cheers.
It's so hot.
Delicious!
Let's eat!
I'm here mode job, right?
me you are amazing b ultimate
hd
bic a
Soft and chewy
Soft and chewy.
Mmmm
It's so good!
I'd love some sushi.
You want some?
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
I'm so happy about the second one.
How much better is it today?
It's one times better today.
It's not going to change.
Buber 1ka Kreio.
disappointed 2
Oh, it's good for me too!
Boo Boo!
I'm going to do my best to get a good job.
I'm going to do some sports and I'm going to do some sports and I'm going to do some sports and I'm going to do some sports and I'm going to do some sports
I want to do sports, I want to do sports, I want to do sports, I want to do sports, next, I want to evolve
I want to do sports, next time I want to evolve and do marine sports and have a barbecue
I can't do that!
Eating...
How do you eat with a spoon?
I can always tell which part of the body you're eating when I look at you like this.
zaczy prisoners
7 up here
cr
Perfect.
I'm sorry, but as beloved as I am, I've been a hawk lately.
I laughed so hard on the way home.
I laughed so hard today that I got a stomach ache.
I'm sure we'll do it again today. Let's eat sushi.
Let's eat! Let's all eat three sushi together.
I'll have one. It's good.
I wonder if I can make it. One bite.
No one can talk.
Bon appétit!
Big. It's big.
It melts in your mouth.
It melts in your mouth. Wow.
And the tour... the national tour...
We're almost at the end of the tour now, but Fukushima and Kumamoto are still out there.
That's right! I was so nervous!
Do you have any memories?
I still remember singing solo.
I'll never forget the view, and I'll probably remember it right before I die.
I really think so.
I'm sure I'll remember it like it was amazing.
I remember watching Mirei practicing in the lesson room with earphones in.
I was so happy to be able to go to the Fukushima live show.
I was so happy to go to the live in Fukushima.
Thank you so much for going to Iwaki, too!
I hope to go back to Iwaki and have dinner with you again!
I'm so happy that we could all go to Kumamoto together!
I can't replace it...
Hey, hey, hey... a lot of Kumakuma members here!
Boo Boo... we had the best food on this tour.
I'll write about it in the comments section.
I want you to write about it. I want to hear about it.
We don't want the tour to be over when it's open to the public.
I want to go around again.
But... we're in the same age group... but... we spent our school life in different places.
But because we were in the same class...
We're in the same class.
We can be...
I can be...
That makes me happy, doesn't it?
But I thought about it a lot, Sayamon. I think it's because I've been accepted by Noimi and I've been working with her.
We are actually the same age, but six years younger? Natsumi...
The members are different ages, and the fans are young and old, male and female.
We are all in the same class.
Everyone is talking about it in their posts.
That's what I like about it.
When's the next post?
We've always been in the same class.
That's right.
We've been in the same class forever.
Yes, so we had a lot of it.
After this, too, it was delicious!
There's still a lot more.
I'd like to eat them.
I hope you and Noumi will continue to have fun in the summer.
I hope you can enjoy the summer as well.
I hope you will enjoy this video, this summer, fall, and winter.
We also have our 9th single!
I think it will be released soon.
Let's go through our youth with Emi-chan!
Let's run through our youth!
Delicious barbecue today!
Thank you very much!